(Sheldon:)Electrons move through graphene,
act as if they have no mass.
(Howard:)How long has he been stuck?
Mm, intellectually, about 30 hours.
(Leonard:)Emotionally, about 29 years.
(Sheldon:)Unit cell contains two carbon atoms.
(Sheldon:)Interior angle of a hexagon
is 120 degrees.
(Howard:)Have you tried rebooting him?
[BOTH LAUGHING]
(Leonard:)No. I think it's a firmware problem.
(Raj(arriving):)Hey, it's disco night
at the Moonlight Roller Rink tonight.
(Raj(arriving):)Who's up for getting down?
(Howard:)Oh, that's perfect.
Bernadette's been hawking me
to take her roller skating.
(Leonard:)Penny likes to skate.
The four of us could double.
(Howard:)We're in.
(Raj:)Great. It's not like I brought it up
because I wanted to go.
(Howard:)-You can come with us.
-No. I don't have to go.
(Raj:)I'm happy just to guide you
to suitable entertainment choices.